[
    {
      "Question": "It involves eliciting information from the customer about the work environment, or domain, in which the final product will function in life cycle.",
      "CorrectAnswer": "Requirements Specification",
      "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
      "Question": "It is the first activity that has a high-level decomposition of the system into components that can either be brought in from existing software products or be developed from scratch independently.",
      "CorrectAnswer": "Architectural Design",
      "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
      "Question": "It is an architectural design that provides a decomposition of the system description that allows for isolated development of seperate components which will later be integrated.",
      "CorrectAnswer": "Detailed Design",
      "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
      "Question": "It is a detailed design for a component of the system should be in such a form that it is possible to implement it in some executable programming language.",
      "CorrectAnswer": "Coding and Unit Testing",
      "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
      "Question": "It is once enough components have been implemented and individually tested, they must be integrated as described in the architectural design.",
      "CorrectAnswer": "Integration and Testing",
      "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
      "Question": "It is all work on the system is considered under the category of maintenance, until such time as a new version of the product demands a total redesign or the product is phased out entirely",
      "CorrectAnswer": "Maintenance",
      "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
      "Question": "It is the ultimate test of usability based on measurement of user experience. It demands that specific usability measures be made explicit as requirements",
      "CorrectAnswer": "Usability Engineering",
      "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
      "Question": "4 Specifications of Usability",
      "CorrectAnswer": "Usability Attribute/Principle, Measuring Concept, Measuring Method, New Level/Worst Case/Planned Level/BestCase",
      "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
      "Question": "It is a usability specification that requires level of detail that may not be possible early in design satisfying a usability specification does not necessarily satisfy usability",
      "CorrectAnswer": "Problems",
      "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
      "Question": "It overcomes inherent problems of incomplete requirements",
      "CorrectAnswer": "Iterative Design",
      "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
      "Question": "4 management issues in Iterative design",
      "CorrectAnswer": "Time, Planning, Non-Functional Features, Contracts",
      "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
      "Question": "Four Main Phases in Software Process + the Iteration Loop that is focused on the design of interaction",
      "CorrectAnswer": "What is wanted, Analysis, Design, Prototype, Implement and Deploy",
      "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
      "Question": "It is the first stage in four main phases of software process that is establishing what exactly is needed",
      "CorrectAnswer": "What is wanted",
      "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
      "Question": "It is the result of observation and interview in 4 main phases in software cycle, need to be ordered in some way to bring out key issues and communicate with later stages of design.",
      "CorrectAnswer": "Analysis",
      "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
      "Question": "The central stage in 4 main phases of software cycle when you move from what you want, how to do it.",
      "CorrectAnswer": "Design",
      "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
      "Question": "Tt is the process in 4 main phase of software cycle that the system is producing its early version to try out with real users",
      "CorrectAnswer": "Iteration and Prototyping",
      "FakeAnswers": []
    },
  {
    "Question": "The last phase in 4 main phase of Software Cycle that after the design, it is needed to be create and deploy. It involves writing code, documentations and manual",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Implementation and Deployment",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  
  {
    "Question": "It involves eliciting information from the customer about the work environment, or domain, in which the final product will function in life cycle.",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Requirements Specification",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is the first activity that has a high-level decomposition of the system into components that can either be brought in from existing software products or be developed from scratch independently.",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Architectural Design",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is an architectural design that provides a decomposition of the system description that allows for isolated development of seperate components which will later be integrated.",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Detailed Design",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is a detailed design for a component of the system should be in such a form that it is possible to implement it in some executable programming language.",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Coding and Unit Testing",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is once enough components have been implemented and individually tested, they must be integrated as described in the architectural design.",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Integration and Testing",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is all work on the system is considered under the category of maintenance, until such time as a new version of the product demands a total redesign or the product is phased out entirely",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Maintenance",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is the ultimate test of usability based on measurement of user experience. It demands that specific usability measures be made explicit as requirements",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Usability Engineering",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "4 Specifications of Usability",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Usability Attribute/Principle, Measuring Concept, Measuring Method, New Level/Worst Case/PlannedLevel/BestCase",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is a usability specification that requires level of detail that may not be possible early in design satisfying a usability specification does not necessarily satisfy usability",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Problems",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "It overcomes inherent problems of incomplete requirements",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Iterative Design",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "4 management issues in Iterative design",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Time, Planning, Non-Functional Features, Contracts",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "Four Main Phases in Software Process + the Iteration Loop that is focused on the design of interaction",
    "CorrectAnswer": "What is wanted, Analysis, Design, Prototype, Implement and Deploy",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is the first stage in four main phases of software process that is establishing what exactly is needed",
    "CorrectAnswer": "What is wanted",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is the result of observation and interview in 4 main phases in software cycle, need to be ordered in some way to bring out key issues and communicate with later stages of design.",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Analysis",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "The central stage in 4 main phases of software cycle when you move from what you want, how to do it.",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Design",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "It is the process in 4 main phase of software cycle that the system is producing its early version to try out with real users",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Iteration and Prototyping",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "The last phase in 4 main phase of Software Cycle that after the design, it is needed to be create and deploy. It involves writing code, documentations and manual",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Implementation and Deployment",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  
  {
    "Question": "This is a collection of processess, which focus on putting users at the center of the product",
    "CorrectAnswer": "User Centered Design",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "This is an iterative design process in which designers and other stakeholders focus on the users and their needs in each phase of the design process. This calls for involving users throughout the design process",
    "CorrectAnswer": "User Centered Design",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "Users should be able to see from the beginning what they can do with the product, what is it about, how they can use it.",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Visibility",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "Users should be able to find information easily and quickly.",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Accessibility",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "Text should be easy to read and understand.",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Legibility",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "Short sentences are preferred here.",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Language",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "A quest to find the best possible match between the user's mental model that they have in their mind, and the conceptual model that you're presenting to them with your product.",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Design",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "This refers to a user's underlying expectations about how something should work. It is formed based on what they already do, prior experiences with similar products, or by assumptions they've made based on how it appears",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Mental Model",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "This is constantly evolving and subject to change. It is influenced by new experiences with your product, other technologies, and day to day life.",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Mental Model",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "This is created by the designer as a high-level plan for how the product will work and fit together.",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Conceptual Model",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "This refers to the structure and grouping of Information within the product",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Information Architecture",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "These are the guiding concepts or rules for the types of content appearing on each page",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Content Strategy",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "This refers to creating consistent, continuous, or complementary experiences?",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Design Language",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "This refers to the usage of well-known patterns and conventions and the interaction of the users to the system.",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Interaction models",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "This refers to a rhetorical device in which a word or phrase literally denoting one kind of object or idea is used in place of another to suggest a likeness or analogy between them.'",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Metaphor",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "This states that an interface should implemented behavior from system that the users are familiar with. It increases the understandability of even most complex application by introducing the element of being familiar with the environment user has been working.",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Principle of Metaphor",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "This metaphor focuses on justice, equilibrium, and the interplay of elements",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Balance",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "This metaphor includes changes in substance and circumstances",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Transformation",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "This metaphor involves the meeting of past, presetn and future.",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Journey",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "This metaphor involves encompassing inclusion, exclusion, states of being, and other boundaries",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Container",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "This metaphor focuses on the need to relate to oneself and others",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Connection",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "This metaphor involves acquisitions and their consequences",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Resource",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
  {
    "Question": "This metaphor involves the sense of mastery, vulnerability, and well-being",
    "CorrectAnswer": "Control",
    "FakeAnswers": []
  },
    {
        "Question" : "A computer program that handles the output to the display and the input from the person using the program.",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "User Interface",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This is recognized as one of the most important elements of a software project. It had been estimated that 48% of work on a project goes into the design and implementation of the user interface depends, among other things, on the designer's creativity.",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "User Interface",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "How many commonly recognized UI are in use today? (numeric)",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "3",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This UI separates the logical threads of computing from the presentation of those threads to the user, through visual content on the display device. This is commonly done through a window system that is controlled by an operating system's window manager.",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Graphical User Interface",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This UI use speech technology to provide people with access to information and to allow them to perform transactions.",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Voice User Interface",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This UI's development was driven by customer dissatisfaction with touchtone telephony interactions, the need for cheaper and more effective systems to meet customer needs, and the advancement of speech technology to the stage where it was robust and reliable enough to deliver effective interaction.",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Voice User Interface",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This UI is what a person interacts with when using a spoken language application. Auditory interfaces interact with the user purely through sound. Speech is input by the user, and speech or nonverbal audio is output by the system",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Voice User Interface",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "These UI provide opportunity to use non-verbal audio such as background music and earcons to create an auditory environment for the user, and thus creating a unique ―sound and feel‖ for a business or application",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Voice User Interface",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This involves collecting a small amount of a persons voice tocreate a voice template, which is used to enroll a person into asystem and then compare future conversation.",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Speaker Verification",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This synthesizes text into speech. The technology has improved significantly in recent times, and although it does not yet duplicate the quality of recorded human speech, it is still a good option for creating messages from text that cannot be predicted, such as translating web pages for blind users",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Text-to-Speech",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "One of the components of Voice User Interfaces that are recorded or synthesized speech played to the user during the interaction.",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Prompt",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "One of the comonents of Voice User Interfaces are the possible responses users can make in relation to each prompt. The system cannot understand anything outside of this range of possibilities.",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Grammar",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "One of the components of Voice User Interface that determines the actions the system can take in user's response to a prompt.",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Dialog Logic",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This UI attempt to address the problems associated with purely auditory and purely visual interfaces by providing a more immersive environment for human-computer interaction.",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Multi-model User Interface",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This UI is one that relies on the use of multiple human communication channels to manipulate the computer. These communication channels translate to a computer's input and output devices.",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Multi-model User Interface",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This UI requires users to interact with the device with their fingers. It has become a commonly used option due to the popularity of portable devices. You come across touchscreen GUI when you look at almost anything on your phone or tablet.",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Touchscreen GUI",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This UI employs a series of screens, or “menus”. When a user makes a selection by tapping/clicking on the list format or graphics, it takes them to the next menu screen until they complete the desired outcome.",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Menu-driven User Interface",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This UI is a text-based user interface for interacting with PC on a low abstraction level. Generally, this type of menu is not intended for the average user. It is mostly used when working with cloud services or carrying out system administrators responsibilities.",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Command Line Interface",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This principle says that the user should be aware of all the functions and functionalities that is available.",
        "CorrectAnswer" :"Exposure",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "One of the main objectives of this principle is to create the UI so as to make the work easier",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "User Profiling",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This principle says that an interface should be coherent, logical, and easily followed",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Coherence",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This principle says each change in the behavior of the program should be accompanied by a corresponding change in the appearance of the interface. One of the big criticisms of modes in interfaces is when a program that many of the class is bad example programs have modes that are visually indistinguishable from one another.",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "State Visualization",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This principle states that the interface should develop confidence amongst the user by providing them a feeling of safety.The User Interface should ensure that the novice user should not feelhim at risk while accessing the program",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Safety",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This principle states that the user's activity should be limited to a well-defined context unless significant reason is there to support his freedom to access more.Each user action takes place within a given context the current document, the current selection, the current dialog box.",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Context",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This principle says that in order to achieve a task or to get a work done, the accessing methods should not only be abstract but concrete too. Once a user has become experienced with an application, she/he will start to build a mental model of that application. She/he will be able to predict with high accuracy what the results of any particular user gesture will be in any given context",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Shortcut",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This principle states that the inevitable defects in the design of the user interface should be spotted. Generally, it is the fundamental defects in a user interface that the designer of the interface can spot. There are however various kinds of defects that are not easy to spot. The testing of user interface is actually the process of testing of the interface using actual end users.",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "User Testing",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question" : "This principle states that some aspects of the User Interface enjoy more attention of the user than others. The user finds same attributes and aspects of the user interface more attractive as compared to others. The human mind is a highly non-linear and has a perfect coordination with the eyes. Thus our eyes are more observant towards animated areas rather than the static are in an application.",
        "CorrectAnswer" : "Focus",
        "FakeAnswers" : []
    },
    {
        "Question": "It involes designing a user interface to possess human-like qualities",
        "CorrectAnswer": "Anthropomorphic Approach",
        "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
        "Question": "Are the perceivable potential actions that an individual may do with an object",
        "CorrectAnswer": "Affordances",
        "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
        "Question": "It indicates the limitations of user actions.",
        "CorrectAnswer": "Constraints",
        "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
        "Question": "In designing a user interface, this method takes into account the human brain's ability and sensory experience.",
        "CorrectAnswer": "Cognitive Approach",
        "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
        "Question": "It relies on the user's familiarity with another concept as well as affordances to help them understand the actions they should take",
        "CorrectAnswer": "Metaphoric Design",
        "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
        "Question": "In designing an interface, It's important to consider the user's attention span and the mental workload involved in completing a task",
        "CorrectAnswer": "Attention and Workload Models",
        "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
        "Question": "It describes the movement of information from the environment into the human mide and back into the world.",
        "CorrectAnswer": "Human Information Processing Model",
        "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
        "Question": "This approach is useful for examining and comparing the usability of multiple conceptual designs",
        "CorrectAnswer": "Empirical Approach",
        "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
        "Question": "It measures user's task performace is important for determining how intuitive and user-friendly a web page is",
        "CorrectAnswer": "Human Task Performance Measures",
        "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
        "Question": "It is also know as Split Testing which is a technique for comparing different versions of a template or interface to see which one gets the most conversions",
        "CorrectAnswer": "A/B Testing",
        "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
        "Question": "It analyzes the individual components of a user interface in terms of the time it takes to effectively achieve an objective using a process called GOMS (Goals,Operators,Methods,and Selection Rules.)",
        "CorrectAnswer": "Predictive Modeling Approach",
        "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
        "Question": "In Predictive Modeling Approach, it is the tasks assigned to users, such as sending emails to customers",
        "CorrectAnswer": "Goals",
        "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
        "Question": "In Predictive Modeling Approach, it is the helper in user's activities to accomplish a task",
        "CorrectAnswer": "Operators",
        "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
        "Question": "In Predictive Modeling Approach, it is the series of operators and sub-goals that the user uses to accomplish a task",
        "CorrectAnswer": "Methods",
        "FakeAnswers": []
    },
    {
        "Question": "In Predictive Modeling Approach, it is the user's persona decision on which method to achieve a goal in a given situation",
        "CorrectAnswer": "Selection Rules",
        "FakeAnswers": []
    }
    
    
]
